Guide to the Benjamin Everett Jordan Papers, 1896-1974 and undated RL.00651
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files, 1936-1973
  - Public Works, 1958-1972, 43 boxes
    - Flood Control: Yadkin River (High Rock), 1963-1968 (Box 164)
    - Flood Control: Yadkin River (Reddies River Reservoir), 1967-1972 (Box 164)
    - Flood Control: Yadkin River (Roaring River), 1964-1971 (Box 164)
    - Flood Control: Yadkin River (W. Kerr Scott Reservoir), 1942, 1952, 1956-1959, 2 folders (Box 164)
    - Flood Control: Yadkin River (W. Kerr Scott Reservoir), 1960-1971, 3 folders (Box 165)
    - Flood Control: Yadkin River-PeeDee River, 1962, 1968, 1970-1971 (Box 165)
    - Flood Control and Navigation: General, 1952-1958, 2 folders (Box 165)
    - Flood Control and Navigation: General, 1959-1963, 6 folders (Box 166)
    - Flood Control and Navigation: General, 1964-1967, 6 folders (Box 167)
    - Flood Control and Navigation: General, 1968-1969, 5 folders (Box 168)
    - Flood Control and Navigation: General, 1970-1972, 6 folders (Box 169)
    - Flood Control and Navigation: General, 1972-1973 (1 vol. and 1 folder) (Box 170)
    - Flood Control and Navigation: General, 1973 (Box 171)
    - Government Buildings, 1958-1959, 1963-1966, 1968-1972, 3 folders (Box 171)
    - Highway Beautification, 1965, 1967, 2 folders (Box 171)
    - Highway Beautification, 1968 (Box 172)
    - Navigation: Avon Harbor and Channel, 1963, 1965 (Box 172)
    - Navigation: Atlantic Intracoastal Waterway, 1958-1972 (Box 172)
    - Navigation: Beaufort Harbor and Inlet, 1958-1972 (Box 172)
    - Navigation: Belhaven Harbor, 1966, 1972; Black River, 1965-1966 (Box 172)
    - Navigation: Bogue Inlet and Swansboro Harbor, 1957-1972 (Box 172)
    - Navigation: Cape Fear River at and below Wilmington, 1939-1972 (Box 172)
    - Navigation: Cape Fear River above Wilmington, 1958- 1972, 2 folders (Box 173)
    - Navigation: Carolina Beach, 1961-1972 (Box 173)
    - Navigation: Corn Cake Inlet, 1972; Dismal Swamp Canal, 1958-1962, 1970-1972 (Box 173)
    - Navigation: Little River, 1966-1972 (Box 173)
    - Navigation: Drum Inlet, 1958-1972 (Box 173)
    - Navigation: Hatteras Inlet Channel and Rollinson Channel, 1958-1972 (Box 174)
    - Navigation: Lockwoods Folly River, 1958-1960, 1968- 1972 (Box 174)
    - Navigation: Manteo (Shallowbag Bay), 1958-1971 (Box 174)
    - Navigation: Masonboro Inlet, 1959-1972 (Box 174)
    - Navigation: Morehead City Harbor, 1958-1972, 2 folders (Box 174)
    - Navigation: Neuse River, 1959-1968 (Box 175)
    - Navigation: New Bern Channel, 1959, 1967 (Box 175)
    - Navigation: New River, 1962-1972 (Box 175)
    - Navigation: Ocracoke Inlet, 1958-1960, 1965-1972 (Box 175)
    - Navigation: Oregon Inlet, 1959-1971, 3 folders (Box 175)
    - Navigation: Pamlico and Tar Rivers, 1961-1970 (Box 175)
    - Navigation: Pamlico Sound and Beaufort Harbor, 1958-1972 (Box 176)
    - Navigation: Roanoke River, 1965-1972, 2 folders (Box 176)
    - Navigation: Shallotte River, 1959-1960, 1970-1972 (Box 176)
    - Navigation: Silver Lake Harbor, 1960-1972; Southport Harbor, 1960-1966; Stumpy Point Bay, 1958-1961, 1966, 1972 (Box 176)
    - Navigation: Sunny Point Military Ocean Terminal, 1971-1972 (1 folder and 1 vol.) (Box 176)
    - Navigation: Surf City and Topsail Inlet 1958-1966; Tar River 1865-1966; Wanchese 1961; West Onslow Beach 1971-1972 (Box 177)
    - Navigation: Wilmington Harbor, 1959-1972, 3 folders (Box 177)
    - Navigation: Wilmington Harbor (Hilton Bridge Project), 1964-1972 (Box 177)
    - Navigation: Wilmington Harbor (Channel to Hilton RR Bridge), 1967-1972 (Box 177)
    - Navigation: Wilmington Harbor (NE Cape Fear River Project), 1958-1967 (Box 177)
    - Navigation: Wilmington Harbor (NE Cape Fear River Project), 1968-1972 (Box 178)
    - Navigation: Wright's Creek (Pungo River), 1959-1965 (Box 178)
    - Pollution, 1967-1970 Mar., 5 folders (Box 178)
    - Pollution, 1970 Apr.-Sept., 6 folders (Box 179)
    - Pollution, 1970 Oct.-1971 June, 5 folders (Box 180)
    - Pollution, 1971 July- 1972, 6 folders (Box 181)
    - Roads, 1968-1970, 6 folders (Box 182)
    - Roads, 1971-1972 Oct., 4 folders (Box 183)
    - Small Watershed Projects: General, 1958-1971, 2 folders (Box 183)
    - Small Watershed Projects: Ahoskie Creek 1960-1961; Back Swamp 1965, 1969-1970; Bryant Swamp 1970-1972; Cane Creek 1968-1970; Chicod Creek 1966-1972 (Box 184)
    - Small Watershed Projects: County Line Creek 1969- 1972; Crabtree Creek 1964-1972; Dutchman's Creek 1964-1972; Flea Hill 1971-1972 (Box 184)
    - Small Watershed Projects: Haw River 1959-1964; Little Contentnea Creek 1966, 1971-1972; Little Yadkin River 1965-1966; Lyon Swamp-White Oak 1964-1966; Mid-East Resource Conservation and Development 1972; Second Broad River 1971; Shoal Creek 1966 Tallulah Creek 1972 (Box 184)
    - Water Miscellaneous: Photographs (6) of Lake Junaluska, N.C., (1966?) (Box 184)
    - Water Miscellaneous: Saline Water Research, 1959-1960 (Box 184)
    - Water Miscellaneous: Soil and Water Conservation Research, 1960 (Box 184)
    - Water Miscellaneous: Stream Pollution, 1962-1965 (Box 184)
- United States Government Branches and Departments Files, 1958- 1972
  Primarily correspondence from constituents for whom Jordan served as intermediary with appropriate government agencies, with replies from the agencies and the Senator's office. Arranged alphabetically by branch or department, then chronologically within each agency. Prominent topics include school desegregation (Dept. of HEW), National Park Service (Interior), and Federal Highway Administration (Transportation).
  - Appalachian Regional Commission, 1965-1970 (Box 185)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1958-1972 (Box 185)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1958-1970 (Box 185)
  - Department of Agriculture
    - General, 1958-1966 Mar., 5 folders (Box 186)
    - General, 1966 Apr.-1970, 5 folders (Box 187)
    - General, 1971-1972, 4 folders (Box 188)
    - Agricultural Marketing Service, 1959-1962, 2 folders (Box 188)
    - Agricultural Marketing Service, 1963-1965 (Box 189)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, 1958-1968, 4 folders (Box 189)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 190)
    - Earl Butz Nomination, 1971 (Box 190)
    - Consumer and Marketing Service, 1966-1969, 2 folders (Box 190)
    - Consumer and Marketing Service, 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 191)
    - Cotton, 1967-1969, 1971-1972, 2 folders (Box 191)
    - Farmers Home Administration, 1961-1970, 2 folders (Box 191)
    - Farmers Home Administration, 1971-1972 (Box 192)
    - FHA Rural Housing Program, 1971 (Box 192)
    - Hurricane Damage, 1971 (Box 192)
    - Forest Service, 1961, 1963-1972, 3 folders (Box 192)
    - Rural Electrification Administration, 1959-1971 (Box 193)
    - School Lunch Program, 1966 (Box 193)
    - Soil Conservation Service, 1959-1971, 2 folders (Box 193)
    - Tobacco, 1966 (Box 193)
    - Tobacco, 1967-1972, 4 folders (Box 194)
  - Department of Commerce
    - General, 1960-1964, 2 folders (Box 194)
    - General, 1965-1972, 4 folders (Box 195)
    - Area Redevelopment Administration, 1961-1966 (Box 195)
    - Bureau of International Commerce, 1970, 1972 (Box 195)
    - Bureau of Public Roads, 1958-1967, 2 folders (Box 196)
    - Bureau of Public Roads (Bryson City/Fontana Road), 1960-1961, 2 folders (Box 196)
    - Bureau of Standards, 1967, 1971, 2 folders (Box 196)
    - Cape Fear Technical Institute, 1971 (Box 197)
    - Coastal Plains Regional Commission, 1972 (Box 197)
    - Economic Development Adminsitration, 1966-1972, 2 folders (Box 197)
    - Environmental Sciences Service Administration, 1967, 1970 (Box 197)
    - Walnut Logs and Veneer Export Controls, 1970 (Box 197)
    - Weather Bureau, 1959-1961, 1963-1964 (Box 197)
  - Department of Defense
    - General, 1958, 1960-1969, 6 folders (Box 198)
    - General, 1970-1972, 5 folders (Box 199)
    - Air Force, 1958-1961 (Box 199)
    - Air Force, 1962-1972, 3 folders (Box 200)
    - Army: General, 1958, 1960-1969, 3 folders (Box 200)
    - Army: General, 1970-1972, 3 folders (Box 201)
    - Army: Calley Trial, 1970 Mar.-Sept., 3 folders (Box 201)
    - Army Corps of Engineers, 1960-61, 1964-1966, 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 201)
    - Army: Nerve Gas, 1970 (Box 202)
    - Civil Defense, 1962 (Box 202)
    - Defense Supply Agency, 1967, 1969 (Box 202)
    - Marine Corps, 1958, 1965, 1972 (Box 202)
    - National Guard Bureau, 1967-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 202)
    - Navy, 1958-1969, 3 folders (Box 202)
    - Navy, 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 203)
  - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare
    - General, 1958-1960, 1962-1964, 1966-1969, 4 folders (Box 203)
    - General, 1970-1972, 3 folders (Box 204)
    - Adult Education, 1967 (Box 204)
    - Beaver Creek Head Start Program (Fayetteville, N.C.), 1972 (Box 204)
    - Blackman's Development Center (Washington, DC), 1972 (Box 204)
    - Food and Drug Administration, 1959-1960, 1962-1965 (Box 204)
    - Food and Drug Administration, 1966-1972, 4 folders (Box 205)
    - Food and Drug Administration: Combination Drugs, 1971 (Box 205)
    - Hospital Reimbursement, 1971 (Box 205)
    - National Institutes of Health, 1962, 1967, 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 205)
    - Office of Education, 1959-1960, 1964-1967, 6 folders (Box 206)
    - Office of Education, 1968-1972, 3 folders (Box 207)
    - Public Health, 1958, 1960-1961, 1963-1965, 3 folders (Box 207)
    - Public Health, 1966-1967, 1969-1972, 4 folders (Box 208)
    - Public Health: Hospitals, 1971 (Box 208)
    - School Desegregation: General, 1969-1970, 2 folders (Box 208)
    - School Desegregation: General, 1971-1972, 3 folders (Box 209)
    - School Desegregation: Alamance County, 1968-1970, 2 folders (Box 209)
    - School Desegregation: Beaufort-Currituck Counties, 1968-1970 (Box 209)
    - School Desegregation: Davidson-Edgecombe Counties, 1968-1970 (Box 210)
    - School Desegregation: Forsyth County, 1970, 2 folders (Box 210)
    - School Desegregation: Franklin-Guilford Counties, 1968-1970 (Box 210)
    - School Desegregation: Halifax-Martin Counties, 1967-1970 (Box 210)
    - School Desegregation: Mecklenburg County, 1969-1970 Feb., 2 folders (Box 210)
    - School Desegregation: Mecklenburg County, 1970 Feb.- 1970 Oct., 2 folders (Box 211)
    - School Desegregation: Nash-Pitt Counties, 1968-1970 (Box 211)
    - School Desegregation: Randolph-Rutherford Counties, 1968-1970 (Box 211)
    - School Desegregation: Sampson-Union Counties, 1968-1970 (Box 211)
    - School Desegregation: Vance County, 1967-1970 (Box 211)
    - School Desegregation: Wake County, 1967 (Box 211)
    - School Desegregation: Wake County, 1968-1970, 2 folders (Box 212)
    - School Desegregation: Warren-Wilkes Counties, 1968-1970 (Box 212)
    - School Desegregation: Wilson-Yadkin Counties, 1969-1970 (Box 212)
    - School Desegregation: Bussing, 1971 Aug.-Sept., 3 folders (Box 212)
    - School Desegregation: Bussing, 1971 Oct.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 213)
  - Department of Housing and Urban Development
    - General, 1966-1967 July, 4 folders (Box 213)
    - General, 1971 Aug.-1972, 3 folders (Box 214)
    - Federal Housing Administration, 1967, 1969, 1971-1972, 2 folders (Box 214)
  - Department of the Interior
    - General, 1958-1961, 1963 (Box 214)
    - General, 1964-1972, 6 folders (Box 215)
    - Alaska Pipeline, 1971-1972, 2 folders (Box 216)
    - Back Bay National Wildlife Refuge, 1972, 2 folders (Box 216)
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs, 1959-1962, 1965-1968, 2 folders (Box 216)
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs, 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 217)
    - Coal Shortage, 1970 (Box 217)
    - Fish and Wildlife Service, 1959-1964, 1966-1970, 4 folders (Box 217)
    - Fish and Wildlife Service, 1971-1972 (Box 218)
    - Fishmeal Imports, 1968 (Box 218)
    - Hickel Appointment, 1969 (Box 218)
    - National Park Service, 1958 Jan.-1966 Apr., 3 folders (Box 218)
    - National Park Service, 1966 May-1969, 6 folders (Box 219)
    - National Park Service, 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 220)
    - National Park Service: Transmountain Road, 1968-May 1971, 4 folders (Box 220)
    - National Park Service: Transmountain Road, 1971 (Box 221)
    - Orange County Mining, 1967 (Box 221)
    - Water Pollution Control Administration, 1966-1970 (Box 221)
  - Department of Justice
    - General, 1959-1965, 3 folders (Box 221)
    - General, 1966-1971, 6 folders (Box 222)
    - General, 1972 (Box 223)
    - Butner Prison, 1972 (Box 223)
    - F.B.I., 1958, 1964-1971 (Box 223)
  - Department of Labor
    - General, 1958-1962, 3 folders (Box 223)
    - General, 1963-1968, 6 folders (Box 224)
    - General, 1969, 1971-1972, 4 folders (Box 225)
    - Airline Strike, 1966 (Box 225)
    - Farm Minimum Wage, 1967 (Box 225)
    - Neighborhood Youth Corps, 1966-1969 (Box 226)
    - Seacap, 1970 (Box 226)
  - Department of State
    - General, 1959-1963 Apr., 5 folders (Box 226)
    - General, 1963 May-1969 Apr., 6 folders (Box 227)
    - General, 1969 May-1971 June, 5 folders (Box 228)
    - General, 1971 July-1972, 3 folders (Box 229)
    - Agency for International Development, 1963-1965, 1967, 1969-1970, 2 folders (Box 229)
    - Biafra, 1969 (Box 229)
    - Ceramic Tile Imports, 1967-1968 (Box 229)
    - Israel, 1967 (Box 230)
    - Kennedy Round, 1967-1968 (Box 230)
    - Pakistan, 1971 Apr.-1972, 2 folders (Box 230)
    - Middle East, 1968-1969, 2 folders (Box 230)
    - Middle East, 1970 Jan.-1972, 4 folders (Box 231)
    - Panama Canal, 1967 (Box 231)
    - Peace Corps, 1962, 1966 (Box 231)
    - Pueblo Incident, 1968 (Box 232)
    - Pueblo Inquiry, 1969 (Box 232)
    - Rhodesia, 1967 (Box 232)
    - Territorial Fishing Rights, 1970-1972 (Box 232)
    - Textile Imports, 1967-1970, 3 folders (Box 232)
    - USSR-US Fishing Negotiations, 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 233)
  - Department of Transportation
    - General, 1967-1971, 4 folders (Box 233)
    - General, 1972 (Box 234)
    - Coast Guard, 1970, 1972 (Box 234)
    - Federal Aviation Administration, 1967 Apr.-1970, 4 folders (Box 234)
    - Federal Aviation Administration, 1971-1972 (Box 235)
    - Federal Aviation Administration: Airlines, 1970 (Box 235)
    - Federal Aviation Administration: Air Traffic Limitations, 1968-1969 (Box 235)
    - Federal Highway Administration, 1969-1971, 3 folders (Box 235)
    - Federal Highway Administration, 1972 (Box 236)
    - Federal Highway Administration: Additional Interstate Mileage, 1968 (Box 236)
    - Federal Highway Administration: Beaucatcher Mountain 1968-1972, 2 folders (Box 236)
    - Federal Highway Administration: Bureau of Public Roads, 1967 (Box 236)
    - Federal Highway Administration: Farm Regulations, 1971 (Box 236)
    - Federal Highway Administration: Philadelphia Plan, 1969 (Box 236)
    - Federal Highway Administration: Motor Carrier Safety Regulations, 1969 (Box 237)
    - Interstate 40, 1971-1972 (Box 237)
    - Joyce Kilmer Memorial Forest, 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 237)
    - Railpax, 1971 (Box 237)
    - Railroad Strike, 1971 (Box 237)
    - Tires, 1971 (Box 237)
  - Department of the Treasury
    - General, 1959, 1961-1964, 1966-1972, 3 folders (Box 238)
    - Bureau of Customs, 1969 (Box 238)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, 1971-1972 (Box 238)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1964-1972 (Box 238)
    - Executive Branch: General, 1960-1972 (Box 238)
    - Federal Communications Commission, 1958, 1960-1972, 3 folders (Box 239)
    - Federal Home Loan Bank Board, 1963-1972 (Box 239)
    - Federal Power Commission, 1965-1971 (Box 239)
    - Federal Reserve System, 1968-1970, 1972 (Box 239)
    - Federal Trade Commission, 1958-1971 (Box 239)
    - General Services Administration, 1958-1969 (Box 239)
    - Housing and Home Finance Agency, 1958-1965 (Box 240)
    - Independent Agencies: General, 1958-1972, 2 folders (Box 240)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1958-1962, 1966-1972 (Box 240)
    - Judicial Branch: General, 1963-1964, 1969-1970 (Box 240)
    - Judicial Branch: Supreme Court, 1958-1959, 1962-1971, 2 folders (Box 240)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1961-1970 (Box 241)
    - National Labor Relations Board, 1958-1971 (Box 241)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity, 1966-1972, 4 folders (Box 241)
    - Office of Emergency Preparedness, 1964-1971 (Box 242)
    - Office of the President, 1961-1972, 2 folders (Box 242)
    - Office of Trade Negotiations, 1964-1969 (Box 242)
    - Selective Service System, 1960-1972 (Box 242)
    - Small Business Administration, 1958-1972, 2 folders (Box 242)
    - Tariff Commission, 1958-1972 (Box 243)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1958-1969 (Box 243)
    - Veterans' Administration: General, 1958-1972 (Box 243)
- North Carolina Government Branches and Departments Files, 1958- 1972
  Material documenting Jordan's contact with agencies of North Carolina state government, usually on behalf of constituents. Arranged alphabetically by agency, then chronologically.
  - General, 1958-1967 Apr., 5 folders (Box 243)
  - General, 1967 May-1972 Apr., 6 folders (Box 244)
  - General, 1972 May-Dec. (Box 245)
  - General: Soul City, 1969 (Box 245)
  - Board of Health, 1959, 1970-1972 (Box 245)
  - Department of Conservation and Development, 1959-1972 (Box 245)
  - Department of Conservation and Development: Baldhead Island (Smith Island), 1970-1972 (Box 245)
  - Department of Justice, 1958-1971 (Box 245)
  - Department of Public Instruction, 1959, 1965- 1967, 1969 (Box 245)
  - Department of Social Services, 1970-1971 (Box 245)
  - Department of Water and Air Resources, 1961-1971, 2 folders (Box 245)
  - Department of Water and Air Resources: Yadkin River Fish Kill, 1970-1971 (Box 246)
  - General Assembly, 1963-1965, 1969, 1971 (Box 246)
  - Highway Commission, 1958-1972, 5 folders (Box 246)
  - North Carolina Fund, 1967-1968 (Box 246)
  - Ports Authority, 1961-1972 (Box 246)
  - Seashore Commission, 1962-1969, 2 folders (Box 247)
  - Utilities Commission, 1959, 1961-1962 (Box 247)
  - Utilities Commission: Natural Gas, 1970-1971 (Box 247)
  - County and Local Projects
    - General, 1966-1972 (Box 248)
    - Aberdeen; Ahoskie (Box 248)
    - Alamance Co., 1968-1972 (Box 248)
    - Albermarle; Alexander Co.; Alexander Mills; Alleghany Co.; Andrews; Angier; Anson Co.; Apex; Appalachia (Eastern); Asheboro; Ashe Co. (Box 248)
    - Asheville, 1968-1972 (Box 248)
    - Avery Co.; Ayden; Bailey; Bakersville; Banner Elk; Bath (Box 248)
    - Beaufort, 1966-1972 (Box 248)
    - Beaufort Co.; Belhaven; Belmont; Bennett; Benson; Bertie Co.; Bethel; Biscoe; Bladen Co.; Bladenboro; Blowing Rock; Bogue Banks; Boiling Springs; Bolivia; Boone; Boonville; Brevard; Broadway (Box 248)
    - Brunswick Co., 1968-1969 (Box 248)
    - Bryson City; Buncombe Co.; Bunn; Burgaw; Burke Co. (Box 248)
    - Burlington, 1967-1971 (Box 248)
    - Burnsville; Cabarrus Co. (Box 249)
    - Caldwell Co., 1966-1972 (Box 249)
    - Calypso; Camden Co.; Candor; Canton; Carolina Beach Carrboro; Carteret Co.; Carthage; Cary; Caswell Co.; Catawba Co.; Chadbourn (Box 249)
    - Chapel Hill, 1967-1971 (Box 249)
    - Charlotte, 1966-1972, 2 folders (Box 249)
    - Chatham Co.; Cherokee Co.; Cherokees (Eastern Band) Chimney Rock; Chowan Co.; Clarkton; Clay Co.; Clayton; Cleveland Co.; Clinton; Clyde (Box 249)
    - Columbia, 1972 (Box 249)
    - Columbus; Columbus Co.; Concord; Conover; Conway; Craven Co.; Cumberland Co.; Cumnock; Currituck Co.; Dare Co.; Davidson Co.; Davie Co.; Denton; Dillsboro; Dobson; Dover; Drexel; Dunn; Duplin Co. (Box 249)
    - Durham, 1966-1972 (Box 249)
    - Durham Co. (Grant Application), 1968 (Box 250)
    - East Bend; Eden; Edenton; Edgecombe Co.; Elizabeth City; Elkin; Elm City; Enfield; Englehard; Erwin; Fair Bluff; Fairmont; Faison; Faith; Falcon; Farmville (Box 250)
    - Fayetteville, 1964-1970 (Box 250)
    - Fletcher; Forest City; Forsyth Co.; Franklin; Franklinton; Fremont; Garner; Gaston; Gaston Co.; Gastonia; Gates Co.; Gatesville; Goldsboro; Goldston; Graham (Box 250)
    - Granite Falls; Granite Quarry; Grantsboro; Granville Co.; Greene Co. (Box 250)
    - Greensboro, 1967-1968 (Box 250)
    - Greensboro, 1969-1972 (Box 251)
    - Greenville, 1967-1972 (Box 251)
    - Grifton (Box 251)
    - Guilford Co., 1971-1972 (Box 251)
    - Halifax Co.; Hamilton; Harkers Island; Harnett Co.; Havelock; Henderson; Henderson Co.; Hendersonville; Hertford; Hertford Co.; Hickory (Box 251)
    - High Point, 1967-1972 (Box 251)
    - Hillsborough; Hoke Co.; Hyde Co.; Iredell Co. Jackson Co.; Jacksonville; Jefferson; Johnston Co.; Jones Co.; Jonesville; Kannapolis; Kenansville; Kenly; Kernersville (Box 251)
    - King's Mountain, 1968-1972 (Box 251)
    - Kinston; Kittrell; Knightdale; Lake Waccamaw; Landis Laurinburg; Lee Co.; Lenoir; Lewiston; Lexington; Liberty; Lillington; Lincoln Co.; Lincolnton; Littleton; Long Beach; Lowell (Box 252)
    - Lumberton, 1967-1972 (Box 252)
    - McDowell Co.; Macon Co.; Madison; Madison Co. Maiden; Manteo; Marble; Marion; Mars Hill; Marshall Marshville; Martin Co.; Matthews; Maxton; Mayodan Maysville; Mebane; Mecklenburg Co.; Middlesex (Box 252)
    - Mid-East Economic Development District; Mitchell Co. Mocksville; Moncure; Monroe; Montgomery Co.; Montreat; Moore Co.; Mooresboro; Mooresville; Moravian Falls; Morehead City (Box 252)
    - Morganton; Mount Airy; Mount Gilead; Mount Olive; Murfeesboro; Murphy; Nash Co.; Nashville (Box 252)
    - New Bern, 1965-1972 (Box 252)
    - New Hanover Co.; Newland; Newport; Newton; Northampton Co.; North Wilkesboro; Norwood (Box 252)
    - Ocean Isle Beach (Box 252)
    - Okracoke, 1969-1970 (Box 253)
    - Old Fort (Box 253)
    - Onslow Co., 1965-1972 (Box 253)
    - Orange Co.; Oxford; Pamlico Co.; Pasquotank Co.; Peachland; Pembroke; Pender Co.; Perquimans Co.; Person Co.; Pilot Mountain; Pink Hill; Pitt Co.; Plymouth; Polk Co. (Box 253)
    - Princeville, 1966-1971 (Box 253)
    - Raeford (Box 253)
    - Raleigh, 1968-1972 (Box 253)
    - Ramseur; Randleman; Randolph Co.; Red Springs; Reidsville; Research Triangle; Rich Square; Richmond Co.; Roanoke Rapids; Robbinsville; Robersonville; Robeson Co. (Box 253)
    - Rockingham Co., 1965-1972 (Box 253)
    - Rocky Mount; Rosman; Rowan Co.; Roxboro; Rutherford Co.; Rutherfordton; Salemburg; Salisbury; Saluda; Sampson Co.; Sanford; Scotland Co.; Scotland Neck; Selma; Seven Springs; Severn (Box 254)
    - Shelby; Siler City; Smithfield; Snow Hill; Southern Pines; South Mills; Southport; Sparta; Spencer; Spindale; Spring Lake; Spruce Pine; Stanly; Stanly Co.; Stantonsburg; Star; Statesville; Stokes Co.; Stoneville; Stovall; Surf City; Surry Co,; Swain Co.; Swan Quarter; Swansboro; Sylva (Box 254)
    - Tabor City, 1968-1972 (Box 254)
    - Tarboro, 1967-1972 (Box 254)
    - Taylorsville; Thomasville; Topsail Beach; Transylvania Co. (Box 254)
    - Troy, 1969-1972 (Box 254)
    - Tryon; Tyrrell Co.; Union Co.; Vance Co.; Vanceboro; Wadesboro; Wake Co.; Wallace; Walnut Cove; Walstonburg; Warren Co.; Warrenton; Warsaw; Washington; Watauga Co.; Waxhaw; Wayne Co.; Waynesville; Weaverville; Wendell; West Jefferson; White Oak; Whiteville (Box 254)
    - Wilkes Co., 1967-1972 (Box 254)
    - Wilkesboro; Williamston; Wilmington; Wilson; Wilson Co.; Windsor; Winfall; Wingate (Box 255)
    - Winston-Salem, 1967-1972 (Box 255)
    - Winterville; Woodville; Wrightsville Beach; Yadkin Co.; Yancy Co.; Yaupon (Box 255)
    - Zebulon, 1968-1972 (Box 255)
  - College Projects: